CARLO BONILLA MORALES

Alajuela · +506 85011597 carlobonilla640@gmail.com · Carlo Bonilla · LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlo-bonilla-b6a67623a/

Hello, my Full name is Carlo Alejandro Bonilla Morales. I live in Alajuela. I like to be researching the news about my career. That's why I like being self-taught. My English level is B1

Porfolio: https://cabonillamo.github.io/portfolio/

EXPERIENCE

I have basic Knowledge of SQL server management and the following programming languages.

| | May 2021 – December 2021 |
|---|--|
| İ | JAVA Developer Developed desktop applications with java in college. |
| | January 2022 – April 2022 |
| | C# Developer Developed desktop applications with C# in college. |
| | May 2022 – August 2022 |
| | HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Web Developer Developed web applications with JavaScript, html and CSS a bit of react, bootstrap 5 |
| | September 2022 – December 2022 |
| | JAVA Web Developer Developed web applications with JAVA, html, CSS and bootstrap 5. |
| | January 2023 – Currently |
| | C# Web Developer with .NET ASP Developed web applications with C#, html, CSS and bootstrap 5. |

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2021 - Currently

Universidad Técnica Nacional de Costa Rica
Diploma

2013 - 2019

High School CTP de Sabalito
Diploma

SKILLS

- Initiative
- Teamwork
- Leadership

- Creative
- Respectful
- Responsible